http://www.thestage.co.uk/legal/privacy-policy

Search
West EndMusical TheatreBackstage & TechnicalObituaries & ArchiveOperaDanceAwardsJobs & AuditionsTraining & Drama SchoolsHot TopicsBroadway & InternationalActing & PerformanceEdinburgh FringeShakespearePantomime
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Please read and save this Privacy Policy.
Privacy Summary
The Data Controller, The Stage Media Company Limited (hereafter ‘The Stage’), a company registered in the United Kingdom (Registered No. 02316307at 47 Bermondsey Street, London,SE1 3XT) is committed to protecting your privacy in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 (the ‘Act’) and the General Data Protection Regulation (the ‘GDPR’). If you have any questions about this policy, the representative responsible for Data Protection, the Data Protection Officer, can be contacted by writing to the above address or alternatively by sending an email to dpo@thestage.co.uk
The Stage Media Company Limited is a publishing business providing industry information, news and work opportunities.
In order to operate the services we offer, The Stage (‘our’, ‘us’ or ‘we’), must ask you to provide us with information about yourself. This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect and how we use that information. We take the processing of your information very seriously and will use your information only in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, personal data is referred to as ‘information’ which means any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites and we recommend that you check the privacy policy of any other web sites you may visit. The inclusion of links to such web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such sites nor any association with their owners or operators. If you have any complaints relating to such sites, please contact them directly.
This Privacy Policy will be updated from time to time and all future changes will take effect as specified at the time of the update by posting a revised version of it on our website. Please check back regularly for the most current version of our Privacy Policy.
Information We Collect
To use any of our services, you may ask you to provide your name, address, email address and in some instances your company name, job title or function and telephone number. In order to make payments for our paid services, you must provide credit card, debit card or bank account information. If you wish to use our Castings service (found at castings.thestage.co.uk), we may also collect sensitive personal information such as your racial or ethnic origins which will be shown in your profile. This serves a legitimate interest for all parties due to the nature of the product and service. Further details on the information collected by our Castings product can be found on that website.
When you access our services online using any device, we collect and store device data including but not limited to geolocation data to provide offers relevant to your region. We also collect information such as which pages of our website you visit, IP addresses, the type of browser you use and the times you access our website.
We will only keep your information for as long as is necessary for the purpose of providing you with the service you have requested from us or to meet specific anti-fraud and legal requirements. If you would like more information, please contact the Data Protection Officer.
The provision of the information detailed above is a requirement necessary to provide the service. By providing your information and signing up to our service you are entering a contract for the term of the service. If you object or are not willing to provide this information, please do not register or use any of our services.
When you access our website, or use any of our services, we (including companies we work with) may place small data files on your computer or other device known as cookies. For more information, please see our Cookies Policy at www.thestage.co.uk/cookies/
How We Use The Information We Collect
Our primary purpose in collecting your information is to provide you with a service. You agree that we may use your personal information to:
Provide the service to you;
Notify you about your service including reminding you when it is due to lapse;
Carry out internal administration and analysis;
To help us to improve the services we offer;
To provide personalised services unique to individual users;
To use anonymous details about our users to sell appropriate advertising space on the site. This might mean showing an advertiser how many users we have on the site; it does not mean sharing an individual’s details with an advertiser. Where we collect registration information from an individual, we will never share that individual’s information with a third party, including an advertiser, without that user’s explicit permission.
How We Use The Information For Marketing
We will only send you direct marketing communications in circumstances where we have your specific consent or where we believe we can demonstrate a legitimate interest.
When you sign up to any of our services, we ask for your consent to send you direct marketing communication over a variety of channels. We will honour your right to withdraw your consent at any time.
When you enquire about or request a service from us, we may rely on our legitimate business interests to send you marketing communications (via post, email or telephone). These communications will always be related to our services and we believe will be of interest to you.
We will always provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of this when you provide your information to us.
If you want to stop receiving direct marketing from us, you can use the unsubscribe mechanism on any email you receive from us or alternatively you can contact the Data Protection Officer using the details available in the Privacy Summary.
Periodically we conduct data profiling on the information we collect to better understand our customers in order to provide targeted communications which suit your needs. If you wish to stop your information being used for data profiling, please contact the Data Protection Officer. Please note that a request to opt out of data profiling will automatically stop direct marketing from us and vice versa.
How We Share Information With Third Parties
We will not sell or rent your information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your consent.
However, just like most service providers, The Stage works with third parties who administer important functions for us that allow us to offer and enhance the services we provide e.g. a payment gateway to repeat subscription billings. These providers are covered by an appropriate agreement and are located within the European Economic Area. Sometimes it will be necessary for us to disclose information required for the specific purpose to them so that the services can be performed and by requesting us to provide you with the services you consent to this disclosure.
We reserve the right to disclose to third parties your information to comply with applicable laws including but not limited to disclosure in accordance with the Regulation of Investigatory Powers Act 2000 and lawful authority requests, to safeguard the proper operation of our systems and to protect ourselves and the companies we work with.
Information Security
The Stage is committed to handling your information with high standards of information security. We collect, store and process your information on servers primarily located in the United Kingdom but also elsewhere in the European Economic Area. We use safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption, we enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files and we authorise access to personal information only for those employees who require it to fulfil their job responsibilities. Our site uses industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of information during transmissions to our servers. These security measures mean that we may occasionally have to ask you for proof of identity before we are able to disclose personal information to you.
Accessing, Deleting Or Updating Your Information
Accessing Your Information
You can access the personal information you have provided us by making a Data Subject Access Request to the Data Protection Officer using the form located here www.thestage.co.uk/data-subject-access-request. Upon receipt and following any necessary proof of identification checks, Data Subject Access Requests will be responded to within one calendar month.
Deleting Your Information
A request to have the personal information you have provided us removed from our systems can be made to the Data Protection Officer using the details available in the Privacy Summary. Your information will be removed from our systems except in circumstances where we are required to retain this information for compliance with legal obligation or for future suppression purposes, where the minimal amount necessary will be retained in order to honour an individual’s right.
Updating Your Information
You can review the personal information you have provided us and make any desired changes or rectifications at any time either online or by contacting the Data Protection Officer using the details available in the Privacy Summary.
Information Regarding Children
Children aged 13 and older are eligible to use the majority of services we offer and we ask that minors (persons under the age of 13) do not submit any personal information to us. In the case of Castings, we ask that those under 16 do not submit personal information to us, but those between 13 and 16 may do so with parental consent.
Accountability
We will process your personal data for the purposes set out in this policy. However, if you have any queries or requests in relation to Data Protection or this Privacy Policy please notify our Data Protection Officer using the details available in the Privacy Summary. Alternatively, if you have any concerns about our information rights practices that our Data Protection Officer was unable to address sufficiently, you may report these to our statutory authority, the Information Commissions Office: ico.org.uk.
For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), we are registered with the ICO with notification number Z3499412.
Free gift!Subscribe for a year and get a free tote bag Subscribe
© Copyright The Stage Media Company Limited 2020
